(music, music mood, scary music)
Today, you are truly blessed.
Today, you fight for God himself.
Today, you are holy warriors baptized in the blood of our unholy enemies.
Look at that rabble down there, Bayman, just waiting to meet the Lord.
I pity any man whose last face they see is yours, Felson.
...has fallen.
The only sin you will face this day is failure.
Whoever slays the most men drinks for free.
(non-motorized land vehicle, bicycle, sounds of things, vehicle)
I'll take the 300 on the left, you take the 300 on the right.
But if we divide them evenly, who will buy tonight's drinks?
Oh, you're buying, my friend.
Prepare for battle!
Fine.
I'll kill all 600 myself.
(tools, sawing, sounds of things, wood)
No!
(music, glass, shatter, human voice, speech)
I'm building up a powerful search, baby!
You're fine, my friend.
(music, glass, shatter)
The spell-break will blind your paradise!
Ride down for unholy enemies!
(tools, sawing, surface contact, rub, sounds of things, wood)
I will not yield until every enemy of God has fallen!
You ever get the feeling God has too many enemies?
(miscellaneous sources, arrow)
Being his friend is not so easy either!
They are godless people!
Infidels!
They have sinned against God and against his only son, Jesus Christ!
They must be punished!
(tools, jackhammer)
Do not fail him!
Strike down with his vengeance!
Let none survive!
(truck, air brake)
A thousand lost souls for the fires of hell.
A glorious day for the church.
You call this glorious?
Murdering women and children?
Know your place, knight.
You pledge your life to the cause.
For God.
(source-ambiguous sounds, silence)
Not for this.
I am the herald of God in this world.
His voice rings ever in my ears.
Perhaps it is not his voice you hear.
How dare you!
I am the voice of the church, bathed in truth and blameless in the light of my Lord.
You are no more than a rogue with blood on his hands.
Who controls your insolent tongue, Bayman?
(music, music mood, happy music)
Let's get the hell out of here.
You cannot leave.
Who's going to stop us?
(music, music mood, sad music)
Sheep roaming free and no shepherd in sight.
Did they jump the fence?
All of them.
We've been walking all day and haven't passed the soul.
Keep your souls.
Let me find a chicken.
(arrow, human locomotion, run, human voice, speech, animal)
Is anyone here?
Hello?
(non-motorized land vehicle, skateboard)
I haven't seen much death, you and I. Some deserved, some not.
But what does one do to deserve a death like that?
Nothing.
Finally, a town.
We might be recognized.
(clock, clicking, tick)
We should go around them.
Go where?
These horses won't carry us.
They're farm animals.
We need proper horses, food, provisions.
(music, human locomotion, shuffle, human voice, speech)
Please let them come to me!
I beg you!
Me!
(specific impact sounds, basketball bounce)