Marvelous Skook!
It's Unicron!
The ships!
Get to the ships!
It's our only chance!
Hi.
Transformers!
Oh, the beastly eyes!
Robots in disguise!
Transformers!
All of us wage their battle to destroy the evil forces!
Oh, goodness has it come!
It is the year 2005.
The treacherous Decepticons have conquered the Autobots' home planet of Cybertron.
But from secret staging grounds on two of Cybertron's moons, the valiant Autobots prepare to retake their homeland.
Ironhide, report to me at once.
Every time I look into a monitor prime, my circuits sizzle.
When are we gonna start bustin' Deceptichops?
I want you to make a special run to Autobot City on Earth.
But... Listen, Ironhide, we don't have enough energon cubes to power a full-scale assault.
Ready the shuttle for launch.
Your days are numbered now, Deceptichreeks.
Report security status.
No sign of Decepticons here, Prime!
What about Moonbase 2?
Jazz to Moonbase 2!
Bumblebee and Spike here.
We're about to send up with Shadow.
Isn't he set to count shenanigans in your area?
All clear, Jazz.
Hey, Ironhide, tell my son Daniel I miss him.
And tell him not to worry.
I'll be coming home as soon as we've kicked Megatron's tail across the galaxy.
Will do, Spike.
Cliffjumper, commence countdown.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Now, all we need is a little energon and a lot of luck.
Laserbeak returns, Megatron.
Welcome, Laserbeak.
Unlike some of my other warriors, you never fail me.
Soundwave, playback Laserbeak's findings.
As you command, Megatron.
I want you to make a special run to Autobot City on Earth.
Listen, Ironhide.
We don't have enough energon cubes to power a full-scale assault.
Ready the shuttle for launch.
Now all we need is a little energon and a lot of luck.
More than you imagine, Optimus Prime.
The Megatron is simply gone!
Die, Autobot!
I love you.
This was almost too easy, Starscream!
Much easier, almighty Megatron, than attacking the real threat, the Autobots' moon base!
You're an idiot, Starscream!
When we slip by their early warning systems in their own shuttle and destroy Autobot City, the Autobots will be vanquished forever!
No!
Such heroic nonsense!
Fish are jumping today, huh, Danno?
I guess so.
Hey, what's the matter?
Uh, I don't know, Hot Rod.
Come on, you can tell me.
Guess I just miss my dad.
Don't worry, Spike will be back soon.
Oh, hey, I caught something!
Whoa, look at the size of it!
Yep, it's a whopper, all right.
Hot Rod, the shuttle's coming.
Let's watch it land.
Talk about dull, Daniel.
Where are we or what is it?
If you're gonna ride, Danno, ride in style!
Hey, let's stop here!
Why settle for a peak, Daniel, when you can see everything from Lookout Mountain?
A little gentle left, a little bit more.
Terrible revenue, punk.
I'll straighten you out yet.
Hot Rod, look!
There's a hole in the shuttle!
What?
Decepticons!
What's that fool doing?
Attack!
Daniel!
Not bad for an old-timer.
Old-timer?
That's something you'll never believe if you don't get back to the city.
Save it, cop!
Ultra Magnus, a customary evaluation of Decepticon capability indicates a distinct tactical deficiency.
In other words, Perceptor, we're outnumbered.
Pranger, you and R.C.
transform Autobot City.
Perceptor, tell Blaster to radio prime for reinforcements.
What about me, Magnus?
What about me?
I can help.
I want to help.
What about me?
Blur, you can help me alert the others.
Absolutely, positively, definitely.
Nobody gets job done faster than I can.
Nobody, nobody, nobody.
Come on, R.C., let's go.
But Hot Rod and Copper are still outside the city.
We can't wait.
They'll have to take care of themselves.
Come on.
Ascetic fools!
There's no escape!
They're a little heavier than the electrons, Electron!
The Insecticons are in our way!
Wrong!
They're our way in!
shake it under the next fortress blaster ultra magnus sends orders to contact optimus prime on moon base one all right cover your receptors perceptor
Optimus Prime, do you read me?
The Decepticons of Blitzing Autobot City, we're really taking a pounding.
Don't know how much longer we can hold out.
Soundwave, jam that transmission.
Rumble Frenzy, Ravage Ratbat, Eject Operation Interference.
Optimus Prime, do you read me?
The Decepticons of Blitzing Autobot City, we're really taking...
First we crack the shell, then we crack the nuts inside!
Hey!
Run, Blaster!
Save yourself!
No way!
Two can play!
Do you think you got through to Prime?
Let's hope so, because if I didn't, we're all gonna look like burnt-out toaster ovens.
We've got Decepticons in the gates, Decepticons in the air, Decepticons inside the walls, Decepticons, Decepticons, Decepticons.
If we beat them off the walls, initial on the air.
If we shoot them out of the air, the initial of the gates.
So where does that lead us?
Nowhere, that's where.
Come on, RC.
We gotta get this launcher into place.
Megatron's making his big push, and we gotta push back.
Keep at it, springer-boy.
Helps the hand.
Together now.
I was afraid you'd be trapped outside the city.
Hey, I wasn't worried for a microsecond.
Then you probably didn't understand the situation.
I did it.
Constructicons, merge for the kill!
Pop, Hot Rod, look!
and die.
Their defenses are broken!
Let the slaughter begin!
Dinobots, destroy Devastator!
Me Grimlock love challenge!
Dinobots, transform!
Megatron must be stopped, no matter the cost.
One shall stand, one shall fall.
Why throw away your life so recklessly?
That's a question you should ask yourself, Megatron.
No!
I'll crush you with my bare hands!
I've got Te-El Prime!
Stay away, lad!
That's Prime's fight!
You got the power!
Finish him off, Brian!
Do it now!
no more optimus prime grab me mercy i beg of you you who are without mercy now plead for it i thought you were made of sterner stuff no you don't megatron out of the way hot rod
I would have waited an eternity for this.
It's over, Prime.
Optimus, forgive me.
How do you feel, mighty Megatron?
Astrokane, transform and get us out of here!
Don't leave me, Soundwave.
The Decepticons are retreating!
Time did it!
Get your in the dive!
Astrotrain!
Take off!
I fear the wolves are fatal.
Prime, you can't die!
Do not grieve.
Soon, I shall be one with the Matrix.
Ultra Magnus, it is to you, old friend.
I shall pass the Matrix of Leadership as it was passed to me.
But Prime, I'm... I'm just a soldier.
I... I'm not worthy.
Nor was I. But one day, an Autobot shall rise from our ranks.
darkest hour.
you
Jettison some weight, or I'll never make it to Cybertron!
Fellow Decepticons, Astrotrain has requested that we lighten our burden.
In that case, I say it is survival of the fittest!
Do I hear a second on that?
Aye!
And against?
Nay!
The ayes have it!
Get!
Make room for others!
Oh, how it pains me to do this!
Wait, I still function.
Wanna bet?
Stare!
Where?
As Megatron has, how shall we say, departed, I nominate myself as the new leader!
Wait!
The Constructicons form Devastator, the most powerful robot we should rule!
Soundwave's superior.
Constructicons inferior.
Who are you calling inferior?
Nobody would follow an uncharismatic bore like you!
Hey, nobody calls soundwave uncrasmatic!
Yeah, let's kick tailgate!
Constructicons, unite!
Megatron... Welcome, Megatron.
Show yourself.
I have summoned you here for a purpose.
Nobody summons Megatron.
Then it pleases me to be the first.
is my command.
You are to destroy the Autobot Matrix of Leadership.
It is the one thing, the only thing, that can stand in my way.
You have nothing to fear.
I have already crushed Optimus Prime with my bare hands.
You exaggerate.
The point is he's dead, and the Matrix died with him.
Point is, you are a fool.
The Matrix has been passed to their new leader, Ultra Magnus.
Destroy it for me.
Why should I?
What's in it for me?
Your bargaining posture is highly dubious, but very well.
I will provide you with a new body and new troops to command.
And?
And nothing.
You belong to me now.
I belong to nobody!
Perhaps I misjudged you.
Proceed on your way to oblivion.
No!
I accept your terms!
I accept!
Excellent.
Behold, Galvatron.
And these shall be your minions.
Scourge, the tracker.
And his husband, the sweeps.
Cyclonus, the warrior and his armada.
And this shall be
Autobot Matrix will rip open Ultra Magnus and every other Autobot until the Matrix has been destroyed.
To Cybertron!
Destroy the Matrix.
Get on with the ceremony.
My fellow Decepticons, as your new leader, I... Who disrupts my coronation?
Coronation Starscream?
This is bad comedy.
Megatron?
Is that you?
Here's a hint.
Will anyone else attempt to fill his shoes?
What'd he say his name was?
Galvatron.
What is Galvatron?
Galvatron!
Where'd that come from?
Who cares?
I'm more worried about where it's going.
Talk to me, Earth.
We got a situation out here.
Roger me, Wilco me, anything.
Hello, hello, Earth.
I'm picking up a fake signal.
This is Jazz, a ginormous, weird-looking planet that showed up in the suburbs of Cybertron.
And it's attacking Moonbase 1.
Charles, press jumper.
Got the blast free, if we can.
Ignition and hit it!
This is Spike and Bumblebee up here on moon base two.
This thing, this monster planet just ripped the first moon to shreds.
And it's heading this way.
We'll try and slow it down.
But you'd better get here fast because we're not gonna... Dad!
Bumblebee, activate the explosives.
If this doesn't stop at nothing, Will.
The explosives are activated.
Let's get out of here.
Way to go!
Look!
It isn't even dented!
Oh shit, what are we gonna do now?
We're being sucked into it!
How dare Unicron!
Cybertron and all his moons belong to me!
But remember, we belong to him.
I belong to nobody!
I will obey Unicron!
Decepticons to Earth!
Autobots, prepare to board the shuttles.
This new menace is more dangerous than all the Decepticons put together.
Somehow we must destroy it before it devours Cybertron.
But what about my dad?
He's on the moon between that monster planet and Cybertron.
Daniel, we'll do everything we can for Spike.
And what are we gonna do when we get there?
If that thing crunches moons, it'll make short work of us.
Maybe the Matrix can stop it.
You're right, it can.
What do you know about it, lad?
I just got this feeling.
Look!
Another shot of us.
I, Galvatron, will crush you just as Megatron crushed Prime.
And you'll die trying, just like Megatron.
Autobot scrap!
You want me to gut Ultra Magnus?
There are plenty of Autobots for you.
Ultra Magnus is mine!
Stay close to me, Daniel!
And you better stay close to me!
No, you'd better stay close to me.
Nice dino, good dino, sweet dino.
Won't you step into the nice base here for blood?
Pretty please, pretty, pretty, pretty please.
Nice dino, good dino, with sugar on top and a cherry and some whipped cream.
Nice dino, good dino, sweet dino.
Me Grimlock not nice dino.
Me best brains.
Blur, get the Dinobots in the shuttle!
I'm trying to get them into the shuttle, Ultra Magnus, because I know he can't launch the shuttle until I get them into the shuttle, but I can't seem to get them into the shuttle because they're impossible, impossible, impossible!
Okay, forget it.
Cup, Hot Rod, you guys get the Dinobots aboard and get out of here!
Come on, you big bozo, get in the shuttle!
This reminds me of the battle on Alpha-9, the Petro-Rabbits with... Grimlock, get your noodle out of my face!
Me Grimlock love cops' war stories!
You're living one now!
Engage the boosters, for Cybertron's sake!
Tell Grimlock about Petro-Rabbits again!
I'll give you Petro-Rabbits!
Contact!
Looks like we're shipmates, Squirt.
All right!
But if you get space sick, you're gonna walk home.
Hurry!
Wait, Ultra Magnus!
Our sea's still out there!
Thanks.
That was close.
Believe it or not, this is the fun part.
Congratulations, Autobots.
We've lost them.
So rest while you can.
Yep, I remember the dust was so thick off Beta-4, you had to use windshield wipers on your optic sensors.
Me Grimlock know all about wipers.
Want to hear good part of story?
Good part, cop.
Tell Swoop good part.
Okay, okay.
Well, the dust was really thick.
And then this gigantic ickyak came trumping and stomping down the mountain, flames spewing out of its nostrils.
And I thought for sure... Hey, cop, don't you think we have better things to do now than tell old stories?
Like what?
Like maybe figure out how we're gonna rescue our friends and then save Cybertron.
No!
Tell story!
Shh!
Quiet!
Tell story!
We want to hear it!
They're closing on us.
Yep, like the strike bats of Dramadon.
How'd you beat them?
I'm trying to remember.
There were an awful lot of casualties that day.
Oh, yeah, we invented polarities.
They're coming back!
Oh, right, we survived that.
Yeah, but boys survive this.
Cyclonus, transform and attack!
I can't control it!
Cop and Hot Rod just bought it.
I can't deal with that now.
Face it, Magnus.
The Decepticons are gonna dog us until they see us dead.
Then that's exactly what they're gonna see.
Prepare for emergency separation.
That's too dangerous.
What choice do we have?
The Autobots have been terminated.
Excellent.
And the Matrix with them.
No!
Unicrons!
Why?
Take me to Unicron!
Take me now!
Did we have to let him detonate three quarters of the ship?
Seeing as how they would have detonated four quarters, I think it was a good choice.
But now how are we gonna get there in this wreck?
Perceptor, can you locate a place to set down for repairs?
Gamma waves in this sector of space create marginal navigation probabilities.
However... Yes, I believe I can.
The planet of junk is in this vicinity.
Then let's go for it.
Cup!
Grimlock!
Slam!
Anybody!
God!
No!
Cup.
Talk to me.
Fix me.
Sure, Cup.
Right away.
Race for impact!
Say something.
Anybody.
Remind me to give the autopilot a raise.
Daniel?
I'm okay.
Let's try to salvage this thing.
Can I help too?
It's rough out there, kid.
I think Daniel can make himself useful with this.
It was Spike's exosuit.
Dad's exosuit.
He told me all about it.
Here, try it on.
Now try to walk.
Come on, you can do it.
Just think about what you want to do before you do it.
It's kind of tricky.
Whoa!
Keep on practicing.
You'll get the hang of it.
Come on, showtime's over.
We've got work to do.
This must be the junk capital of the universe.
Stop the no-welcome wagonello stranger with that good coffee flavor for you.
Well, you know, I want money back.
Offer expires while you wait.
Operators are standing by.
That does it.
Well, what do you think?
Of all the circuit glitch die-out blowin' them wittery, you left a piece out!
No way!
You're just a little stiff.
Anyway, all things considered, you did an amazing job, lad.
Amazing.
Really?
Yeah, you even got rid of a nasty bar on my rotator.
Now let's find the Dinobots and get off this twisted planet.
Don't act hostile.
I'll use the universal greeting.
Universal greeting?
Watch.
I'll have an idiot out of my hand.
See?
The universal greeting works every time.
Not without making any sudden moves.
Offer them an energy on goody.
This is getting expensive.
Don't worry, they'll reciprocate.
I thought they were supposed to reciprocate.
No more.
Empty.
Reminds me of the Knight of Slave Mind on Galganath VII.
Every place reminds you of someplace else.
Experience, lad.
You should learn to appreciate it.
A lot of good it's done us so far.
Hey, what's going on over there?
Has the Imperial Magistrate reached a verdict?
I have.
Guilty or innocent?
Innocent.
Feed him to the Sharkticons.
What is this place?
The world of the savage-shocked icons and their cruel masters, the Quintessons.
I am Grannix.
My planet was destroyed by Unicron.
Unicron?
Who's Unicron?
A planet that devours everything in its path.
So that's the monster's name.
Oh, please!
I'm the last survivor of LIF!
No!
Let him go!
majestic reached a verdict I have guilty or innocent justice I repeat guilty or innocent
At the end, I'd wish for that.
Me, Swoop, no see nothing.
Me, dreamlock, positive, hot rod and cop clothes.
Me, slag, say you full of the really and the lonely.
Me Grimlock say you full of cesium salami.
Oh, really, I'm bologna.
Primfine, look behind.
Who say that?
You go wrong way, you fool, I say.
Me Grimlock fool.
Picture you got, no fool you not.
Why boy hid my nose?
Really saved my friends today.
Me Grimlock say we on our way.
Eurythron!
Why did you torture me?
No, Unicron!
Ultra Magnus is dead, and the Matrix destroyed!
The Matrix has not been destroyed.
And Ultra Magnus lives on the planet of Junk.
Stock him.
Tear him apart.
And destroy the Matrix.
Be sure the fittings are securely welded.
Absolutely, positively, definitely.
I wouldn't do it any other way, any other way at all.
Whoa, this exosuit's fantastic.
I think I'm starting to get the hang of it.
Forward!
Aventi and I go for the gospel.
Decepticons.
We've got to draw them off and double back to the shuttle.
There goes the shuttle!
What do I do?
Transform!
You can do it!
I know you can do it!
Transform!
Human germ!
There they are!
Attack!
Make a break for cover.
I'll try to unleash the power of the Matrix.
Kill all our one!
Prime, you said the Matrix would light our darkest hour.
Magnus!
I want the Matrix!
Never!
We exterminate him!
Die!
Unicron, my master.
With this, I shall make you my slave.
Before his Imperial Majesty delivers a verdict, would you like to beg for your lives?
It sometimes helps, but not often.
I can't transform.
Keep trying.
Silence, or you'll be held in contempt of this court.
I have nothing but contempt for this court.
Innocent.
They've got more sharkticons than we have photon charges.
Then let's hold a demolition, Davey.
Didn't even bend a fender.
Yeah, but look, there are a lot more of those can-digging, grill-cracking things.
We can't hold out forever, Cup, but we can give them one humongous repair bill.
Excuse me!
Me Grimlock want to munch battle!
I never thought I'd be so happy to see those big bozos.
Me Grimlock no bozo, me king!
Shark dekons, execute them!
Me Grimlock say execute them!
I think the problems on this planet will be solved very shortly.
Yeah, but what about our problems?
We need a ship.
You get ship if I get trip.
Who are you?
Him wheelie.
Him friend.
He'll be mine, too, if he can find a ship.
Gibster, over there.
That's a ship.
Who cares?
As long as it flies.
without the matrix there is no hope no hope no hope no hope at all first prime now ultra magnus what do we do look don't look behind door number two monkey it's time to play end of the line my valentine
It's not hard to knock them down it's getting them to stay
You check in, but you don't check out.
You better squeeze all the time when you can.
But Mr. Whipple's not around.
Put your head in the microwave and get yourself a can.
Take some wooden nickels.
Look, there's a gun.
I'll tell you as she goes, Bob.
Snoopy visitors get mad in the eye by and by.
Film at 11.
It's Hot Rod!
And Cupin the Dinobot!
Guns aren't exactly friendly.
Neither are they, in case you haven't noticed.
What was that universal greeting again?
Never mind.
I remember.
Baweep grana weep ninny bong Baweep grana weep ninny bong Baweep grana weep ninny bong Baweep grana weep ninny bong Baweep grana weep ninny bong
Tell me one last thing.
It's all right.
We can be super long and light.
Come on, join the crowd.
Shout it out loud.
Me Grimlock not kiss her.
Me Grimlock King.
Have a nice day and please pose comfortably for striking, friends.
We fit for rooty soul, say the champions.
Where'd you learn to talk like that?
TV.
We talk TV.
You talk some TV.
I talk some TV.
And now the news.
Don't touch that dial.
Now we run away.
My George Kemosabe's your smashed up friend soon like brand new with 90 day warranty.
Happy birthday!
Look, he's alive!
You're all alive.
The Matrix has gone.
And with it, all hope.
No!
Galvatron has it.
Where's Galvatron?
Where is he?
And the answer is...
Unicron!
Then we've got to destroy Unicron!
Yes, friends!
Act now!
Destroy Unicron!
Kill the Grand Bullseye!
Eliminate even the toughest stains!
No fuss, no mess!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Sail must end!
Rush right on down and test drive ladies' model with no obligation!
New improved junkie on planet Isley Sexy Import with Turbo Handling!
Unicron!
Answer me!
See this!
The Matrix!
I now possess that which you most fear!
You'll do my bidding, or taste my wrath!
You underestimate me, Galvatron.
For a time, I considered sparing your wretched little planet Cybertron.
But now, you shall witness its dismemberment.
No!
Decepticons!
We're under attack!
Scramble!
I don't believe it.
Doesn't this remind you of anything, Cup?
Nope.
Never seen anything like this before.
What happened to Moonbase 2?
Where's my dad?
That's what we're gonna find out.
That did it, Apple.
This is fire, rain and corrosion for up to five years.
Satisfaction guaranteed.
Where's Hot Rod?
I don't know, but I hope they didn't get him.
Quick, this way.
The Matrix!
It will do you no good, Autobot.
It cannot be opened.
Not by a Decepticon.
Like it or not, we are allies now, against a common foe.
That will be obliterated.
Of course, my master!
Puny Autobot!
You lack even Prime's courage!
Me Grimlock kick butt!
Me Grimlock need new strategy!
Daniel!
Dad, what can I do?
Knock down the acid cover!
How?
Blast it, son!
But I don't have a gun!
Use your exosuit!
Daniel!
You did it!
Yeah!
I did it!
Come out, Autobot.
We all must die sometime.
Not today, Galvatron.
I will crush you with my bare hands!
First, Prime.
Then, Ultra Magnus.
And now, you.
It's a pity you Autobots die so easily, or I might have a sense of satisfaction now.
You got the touch!
You got the... Arise, Linus Prime.
This is the end of the road, Galvatron.
Now, light our darkest hour.
Spike, Daniel!
Springer, what's going on?
No time to answer that now.
Let's get out of here!
Look!
Autobots, transform and roll out!
I knew you had potential.
Destiny.
You cannot destroy my destiny!
Let this mark the end of the Cybertronian Wars as we march forward to a new age of peace and happiness.
Till all are one!
You got the time!
You got the power!
We've had a strike, there'll be no place to run When you come within the grill
Robots in the sky Long enough to break the bravest part So we have to pull together No, we can't stay worth the part To stand in line if we was born in war Until our darkest hour
All of us wage their battle to destroy the evil forces of the Decepticons
Coming from the sky above And there's nothing you can do We've had a strike, there'll be no place to run When you come within the grill
Robots in disguise Long enough to break the blade apart So we have to pull together No, we can't stay worlds apart To stand in line if we were strong enough Until our darkest hour
All of us wage their battle to destroy the evil forces of the Decepticons
has been driven from the land.
The battle's over, the war has just begun.
And this weight will remain till the day when all are won.
For the peace we have